Guide to the Stan Healy Photographs and Papers 1890s-1990s (bulk 1940s-1970s)
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Accession 1990-016 Photographs, circa 1890s-1970s; Series I; 6.5 linear feet (2,700 images)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2207)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #2233, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2208)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #2600, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2209)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #3001, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2210)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #9, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2211)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #36, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2212)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #93, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2213)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #215, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2214)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1, the "Minnetoka", undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2215)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2216)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #10, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2217)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1, the "Minnetoka", undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2218)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #2, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2219)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #12, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2220)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #63, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2221)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #145, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2222)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #5(?), undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2223)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #4, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2224)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #14, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2225)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #25, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2226)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #85, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2227)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #185, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2228)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #43, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2229)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #83, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2230)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #155, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2231)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2232)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #8, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2233)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #2222, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2234)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #2628, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2235)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #3102, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2236)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #47, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2237)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #122, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2238)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #252, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2239)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1, the "Minnetoka", undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2240)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #46, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2241)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #46, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2242)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2244)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #240, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2245)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #156, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2246)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #11, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2247)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #695, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2248)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #338, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2249)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #388, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2250)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #635, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2251)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2252)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2253)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2254)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2255)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2256)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2257)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2258)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2259)
  - Women at convention (?), undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2260A)
  - Women at convention (?), undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2260B)
  - Women at convention (?), undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2260C)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #603, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2261)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #684, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2262)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #804, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2263)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #371, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2264)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #469, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2265)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #692, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2266)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #8, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2267)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #676, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2268)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #760, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2269)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #369, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2270)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #412, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2271)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #600, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2272)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #401, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2273)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #367, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2274)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #101, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2275)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #672, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2276)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #149, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2277)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #398, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2278)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #363, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2279)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #645, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2280)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #558, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2281)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #386, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2282)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #328, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2283)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #733, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2284)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #666, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2285)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #583, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2286)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #635, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2287)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1316, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2288)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1844, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2289)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #936, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2290)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1033, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2291)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1175, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2292)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1356, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2293)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1356, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2294)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1912, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2295)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2296)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #943, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2297)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #943, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2298)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1111, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2299)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1212, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2300)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1415, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2301)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #916, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2302)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #952, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2303)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1149, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2304)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1221, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2305)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1529, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2306)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #922, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2307)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #975, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2308)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1159, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2309)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1256, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2310)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1665, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2311)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #924, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2312)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #991, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2313)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1168, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2314)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1293, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2315)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #929, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2316)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1760, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2317)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2318)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1172, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2319)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #1316, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2320)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #943, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2321)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #944, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2322)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Railway locomotive #945, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2323)
  - Missoula fire department, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2324)
  - Missoula fire department, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2325)
  - Missoula fire department, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2326)
  - Missoula fire department, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2327)
  - Missoula's fire horse, "Tyler", undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2328)
  - Missoula's fire horse, "Prince", undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2329)
  - Missoula's fire horses, "Prince and Tyler", undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2330)
  - Missoula's fire horse, "Mock", undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2331)
  - Missoula's fire horse "Snap", undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2332)
  - Fire's destruction, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2333)
  - Missoula fire department, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2334)
  - Fire's destruction, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2335)
  - Missoula fire department, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2336)
  - Missoula fire department champion wet test running team, Missoula, Montana, undated; Same photo as 76-0475; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection (Box 6, Photo number 90-2337)
  - Preparation of Missoula's fire department, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2338)
  - Firemen award presentation, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2339)
  - State Firemen Convention, September 20-22, 1897 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2340)
  - Fire's destruction, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2341)
  - Aerial view of University of Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2342)
  - Missoula firehouse, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2343)
  - Missoula fire department, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2344)
  - Missoula fire department, 1918; Same photo as 76-0288; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection; photographer: R.H. McKay (Box 6, Photo number 90-2345)
  - Missoula fire department wagon #1, 1911; Same photo as 76-0470; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection; photographer: R.H. McKay (Box 6, Photo number 90-2346)
  - Missoula firehouse, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2347)
  - Fire news in Missoula's newspaper, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2348)
  - Fire news in Missoula's newspaper, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2349)
  - Fire news in Missoula's newspaper, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2350)
  - Fire news in Missoula's newspaper, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2351)
  - Fire news in Missoula's newspaper, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2352)
  - Missoula fire department, undated; Same photo as 76-0462; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection (Box 6, Photo number 90-2353)
  - Missoula fire department, undated; Same photo as 76-0465; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection (Box 6, Photo number 90-2354)
  - Missoula fire department, 1911; Same photo as 76-0471; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection; photographer: R.H. McKay (Box 6, Photo number 90-2355)
  - Missoula fire department, undated; Same photo as 90-2344 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2356)
  - Missoula's fire horses, "Mock and Snap", undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2357)
  - Missoula firefighters climbing out a window, undated; Same photo as 76-0292; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection (Box 6, Photo number 90-2358)
  - Missoula fire department, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2359)
  - Missoula fire department mascot, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2360)
  - Missoula fire department, undated; Same photo as 76-0468; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection (Box 6, Photo number 90-2361)
  - Missoula fire department mascot, August 20, 1913 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2362)
  - Missoula firefighters fighting Yandt's fire, January 1, 1942; Same photo as 76-0277; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection (Box 6, Photo number 90-2363)
  - Missoula fire department horses, undated; Same photo as 76-0469; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection (Box 6, Photo number 90-2364)
  - Parade, Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated; Same photo as 76-0464; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection (Box 6, Photo number 90-2365)
  - Yand't fire, Missoula, Montana, January 1, 1942; Same photo as 76-0481; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection; photograher: R.H. McKay (Box 6, Photo number 90-2366)
  - Fire in Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2367)
  - Missoula fire department mascot, undated; Same photo as 90-2362 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2368)
  - Missoula fire department, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2369)
  - Flood of 1908, logjam, Missoula, Montana, circa 1908 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2370)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2371)
  - Bridge of the Bitterroot River branch Railway over Clark Fork River, circa 1908 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2372)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2373)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2374)
  - Flood of 1908, logjam on the Blackfoot River, Missoula, Montana, June 7, 1908; Same photo as 76-0503 (umt010675); photographer: Norman A. Forsyth (Box 6, Photo number 90-2375)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2376)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2377)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2378)
  - Flood of 1908, Higgins Avenue Bridge, Missoula, Montana, circa 1908 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2379)
  - Flood of 1908, Bonner, Montana, circa 1908 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2380)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2381)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2382)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2383)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2384)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2385)
  - Flood of 1908, Bonner, Montana, circa 1908 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2386)
  - Flood of 1908, Bonner, Montana, circa 1908 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2387)
  - Flood of 1908, Higgins Avenue Bridge, Missoula, Montana, circa 1908 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2388)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2389)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2390)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2391)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2392)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2393)
  - Flood of 1908, Bonner, Montana, circa 1908 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2394)
  - Flood of 1908, Bonner, Montana, circa 1908 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2395)
  - Flood of 1908, logjam on the Blackfoot River, Missoula, Montana, June 7, 1908; Same photo as 76-0501 (umt011133); photographer: Norman A. Forsyth (Box 6, Photo number 90-2396)
  - Flood of 1908, Bonner, Montana, Same photo as 76-0502; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection; photographer: Norman A. Forsyth (Box 6, Photo number 90-2397)
  - Flood of 1908, Bonner, Montana, Same photo as 76-0504; photographer: Norman A. Forsyth (Box 6, Photo number 90-2398)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2399)
  - Flood of 1908, Bonner, Montana, circa 1908 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2400)
  - Flood of 1908, Bonner, Montana, Same photo as 76-0500; larger 4x5" negative available in general photo collection; photographer: Norman A. Forsyth (Box 6, Photo number 90-2401)
  - Flood of 1908, Higgins Avenue Bridge (Box 6, Photo number 90-2402)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2403)
  - Flood of 1908, Missoula, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2404)
  - Flood of 1908, Bonner, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2405)
  - Flood of 1908, Bonner, Montana (Box 6, Photo number 90-2406)
  - University of Montana campus, circa 1890s (Box 6, Photo number 90-2407)
  - University of Montana campus, circa 1890s (Box 6, Photo number 90-2408)
  - University of Montana campus, circa 1890s (Box 6, Photo number 90-2409)
  - University of Montana campus, circa 1890s (Box 6, Photo number 90-2410)
  - University of Montana campus, undated; Same photo as 90-2407 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2411)
  - University of Montana campus, circa 1890s (Box 6, Photo number 90-2412)
  - University of Montana campus, circa 1890s (Box 6, Photo number 90-2413)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2414)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2415)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2416)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2417)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2418)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2419)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2420)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2421)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2422)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2423)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2424)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2425)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2426)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2427)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2428)
  - Surgery performed at Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2429)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2430)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2431)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2432)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2433)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2434)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2435)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2436)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2437)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2438)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2439)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2440)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2441)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2442)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2443)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2444)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2445)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2446)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Hospital, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-2447)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2448)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2449)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2450)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2451)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2452)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2453)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2454)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2455)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2456)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2457)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2458)
  - New city council sworn in, Missoula, Montana, May 2, 1977 (Box 6, Photo number 90-2459)